const quiz_questions = [
    {
      // Question 1
      question: "2 x 3?",
      options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      // Question 2
      question: "4 x 5?",
      options: ["15", "18", "20", "25"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      // Question 3
      question: "6 x 3?",
      options: ["12", "15", "18", "21"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      // Question 4
      question: "7 x 2?",
      options: ["12", "14", "16", "18"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      // Question 5
      question: "8 x 4?",
      options: ["24", "28", "32", "36"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      // Question 6
      question: "5 x 5?",
      options: ["20", "25", "30", "35"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      // Question 7
      question: "9 x 3?",
      options: ["24", "27", "30", "33"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      // Question 8
      question: "3 x 8?",
      options: ["20", "21", "22", "24"],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      // Question 9
      question: "6 x 4?",
      options: ["20", "22", "24", "26"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      // Question 10
      question: "2 x 9?",
      options: ["16", "18", "20", "22"],
      answer: 2,
    },
   
  
  

  ];

  export default quiz_questions